{
  "mode": "flash",
  "theme": "world-languages",
  "themeQuestion": "World Languages",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "United States",
      "answer": "English"
    },
    {
      "question": "Brazil",
      "answer": "Portuguese"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cuba",
      "answer": "Spanish"
    },
    {
      "question": "Egypt",
      "answer": "Arabic"
    },
    {
      "question": "Iran",
      "answer": "Persian"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nigeria",
      "answer": "English"
    },
    {
      "question": "Senegal",
      "answer": "French"
    },
    {
      "question": "Vietnam",
      "answer": "Vietnamese"
    },
    {
      "question": "South Africa",
      "answer": "Afrikaans, English and others"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sweden",
      "answer": "Swedish"
    },
    {
      "question": "Thailand",
      "answer": "Thai"
    }
  ]
}
